Brother, what happened today that I overturned the fridge?
Brother, today I was busy searching for money.
But why not see this also now.
Someone will hit you on the head with a slipper.
Hey, she was like a thief, no one would hit her with a slipper or shoot her.
Hey Grandpa.
Brother, today the weather was getting chilly since morning
and in such chilly weather, my uncle and I felt like
eating sweets.  But unfortunately,
brother, my uncle and I did not even have money to buy poison.  Meanwhile,
uncle
told me that he had seen it under the mattresses.  You will definitely get some
money.
[Encouraging voice] [Screaming voice]
But brother, my uncle and I saw the whole mattress.
Uncle saw grandfather's kurta.
We did not get even a single rupee.  There were
so many papers kept under the mattress, brother, as if the entire village
's junk was filled in it.  My uncle and I were busy
searching for money.
Grandfather arrived within this time.  We saw that brother
Dada brought something in a box of sweets.  Uncle
said that you have brought sweets 100% for wisdom.
Grandfather quietly kept the box of sweets
in the fridge and locked it.  Brother, after
seeing this much, I filled the well.   The
lock of the fridge started opening with a jingling sound.
Sometimes with a knife, sometimes with a pliers.  When brother,
all our techniques failed.  The lock did
not open.  We turned the fridge upside down.
While pulling the fridge, the lock also
broke.  Brother, I got a box of sweets,
but as soon as I opened the box, my uncle and my
mood got spoiled because there was onion in it. Uncle was
thinking that it would be rasgullas. I was thinking that
sweets. What did you do
brother? I got sweets and I got 10 more abuses. I do
n't know what the old man will say. See you
in the next blog. Har Har Mahadev.